A Guide to the Island Resources Foundation records FA1200
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Projects and Occasional Papers, 1894-1895, 1946, 1956, 1961-1964, 1968-2016; 3; 33.3 Cubic Feet 85 letter document boxes, 1 half-letter document box, and 1 flat file folder
  - #125, Area of Particular Concern (APC) Management Plans, East End St. Croix Area of Particular Concern Report, 1992 (Box 107, Folder 1174)
  - #125, Area of Particular Concern (APC) Management Plans, Frederiksted Waterfront, 1993 (Box 107, Folder 1175)
  - #125, Area of Particular Concern (APC) Management Plans, Great pond Bay Area of Particular Concern, 1992 (Box 107, Folder 1176)
  - #125, Area of Particular Concern (APC) Management Plans, Salt River Bay Area of Particular Concern Report, 1993 (Box 107, Folder 1177)
  - #125, Area of Particular Concern (APC) Management Plans, Sandy Point Area of Particular Concern, 1993 (Box 107, Folder 1178)
  - #125, Area of Particular Concern (APC) Management Plans, Southgate Pond, Chenay Bay, 1992 (Box 107, Folder 1179)
  - #125, Area of Particular Concern (APC) Management Plans, Southshore Industrial, 1993 (Box 107, Folder 1180)
  - #125, Area of Particular Concern (APC) Management Plans, St. Croix Coral Reef System, 1993 (Box 108, Folder 1181)
  - #126, Jamaica Park Evaluation, Proposal and Work Plan, 1992 (Box 108, Folder 1182)
  - #126, Jamaica Park Evaluation, US Agency for International Development Correspondence, 1992 (Box 108, Folder 1183)
  - #126, Jamaica Park Evaluation, Report, 1992 (Box 108, Folder 1184)
  - #127, PARC (Protected Area Resource Conservation) II, Supplemental Project Paper, Request for Proposal, Proposal, and Contract, 1992 (Box 108, Folder 1185)
  - #127, PARC (Protected Area Resource Conservation) II, Supplemental Project Paper, Personnel and Internal Correspondence, 1992 (Box 108, Folder 1186)
  - #127, PARC (Protected Area Resource Conservation) II, Supplemental Project Paper, 1992 (Box 108, Folder 1187)
  - #128, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) Workshop, Agreement with University of the Virgin Islands and Correspondence, 1992, 1994 (Box 108, Folder 1188)
  - #128, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) Workshop, Announcements, Agenda, etc., 1992 (Box 108, Folder 1189)
  - #128, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) Workshop, Correspondence, 1992, 1994 (Box 108, Folder 1190)
  - #128, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) Workshop, Final Report, 1994 (Box 108, Folder 1191)
  - #129, Anguilla Environmental Profile, Contract and Correspondence with Government, 1992-1995 (Box 108, Folder 1192)
  - #129, Anguilla Environmental Profile, Personnel and Internal Memorandum, 1992-1993 (Box 108, Folder 1193)
  - #129, Anguilla Environmental Profile, Miscellaneous Correspondence, Clippings, etc., 1992-1993 (Box 108, Folder 1194)
  - #129, Anguilla Environmental Profile, National Committee, Correspondence, Minutes, 1992 (Box 108, Folder 1195)
  - #129, Anguilla Environmental Profile, Correspondence with United Nations Development Programme (UNDP), 1992-1994 (Box 108, Folder 1196)
  - #129, Anguilla Environmental Profile, Memorandum of Understanding with Anguilla Archaeological & Historical Society (AAHS), 1992-1993 (Box 108, Folder 1197)
  - #129, Anguilla Environmental Profile, Text, 1993 (Box 109, Folder 1198)
  - #130, Montserrat Environmental Profile, Contract and Correspondence with Government, 1992-1994 (Box 109, Folder 1199)
  - #130, Montserrat Environmental Profile, Personnel and Internal Memorandum, 1992-1993 (Box 109, Folder 1200)
  - #130, Montserrat Environmental Profile, Miscellaneous Correspondence, Clippings, etc., 1993 (Box 109, Folder 1201)
  - #130, Montserrat Environmental Profile, National Committee, Correspondence, Minutes, 1992 (Box 109, Folder 1203)
  - #130, Montserrat Environmental Profile, Memorandum of Understanding and Correspondence with Montserrat National Trust, 1992-1993 (Box 109, Folder 1203)
  - #130, Montserrat Environmental Profile, Correspondence with United Nations Development Programme (UNDP), 1992-1993 (Box 109, Folder 1204)
  - #131, The Moriah Fund, The Nature Conservancy (TNC) Biodiversity, Proposal to Moriah and Award Documents, 1992-1995 (Box 109, Folder 1205)
  - #131, East Caribbean Biodiversity, Proposal to Moriah, 1996-1997, 1999 (Box 109, Folder 1206)
  - #131, The Moriah Fund, The Nature Conservancy (TNC) Biodiversity, Correspondence, 1992-1999 (Box 109, Folder 1207)
  - #131, The Moriah Fund, The Nature Conservancy (TNC) Biodiversity, Nevis Biodiversity Project, 1994, 1997 (Box 109, Folder 1208)
  - #131, The Moriah Fund, The Nature Conservancy (TNC) Biodiversity, Reports to Moriah Fund, 1994-1995, 1997-1998 (Box 109, Folder 1209)
  - #131, The Moriah Fund, The Nature Conservancy (TNC) Biodiversity, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1993-2000, 2002 (Box 109, Folder 1210-1211)
  - #131, The Moriah Fund, The Nature Conservancy (TNC) Biodiversity, Miscellaneous Information, Handouts, etc., 1994-1997 (Box 109, Folder 1212)
  - #131, The Moriah Fund, The Nature Conservancy (TNC) Biodiversity, Internal Correspondence and Personnel, 1994-1997 (Box 110, Folder 1213)
  - #131, East Caribbean Biodiversity Program, Internal Correspondence, 1997-2000 (Box 110, Folder 1214)
  - #131, The Moriah Fund, The Nature Conservancy (TNC) Biodiversity, Dominica Biodiversity Project, 1994-1995, 1997-2000 (Box 110, Folder 1215)
  - #131, The Moriah Fund, The Nature Conservancy (TNC) Biodiversity, Correspondence, Montserrat Project, 1992-1998 (Box 110, Folder 1216)
  - #131, The Moriah Fund, The Nature Conservancy (TNC) Biodiversity, Land Stewardship Workshop, 1993, 1995-1996 (Box 110, Folder 1217)
  - #131, The Moriah Fund, The Nature Conservancy (TNC) Biodiversity, Correspondence, Antigua Project, 1992-1999 (Box 110, Folder 1218-1219)
  - #131, East Caribbean Biodiversity Program, Correspondence, Antigua Project, 2000-2001, 2003-2005 (Box 110, Folder 1220)
  - #131, East Caribbean Biodiversity Program, Office Lease, Antigua's Historical and Archaeological Society, 1997, 1999-2000, 2002 (Box 110, Folder 1221)
  - #131, East Caribbean Biodiversity Program, Kevel Lindsay Reports and Correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 111, Folder 1222)
  - #131, East Caribbean Biodiversity Program, Assistant Director Applications, 1995 (Box 111, Folder 1223)
  - #131, East Caribbean Biodiversity Program, St. Kitts Project, 1996-1997, 1999-2000 (Box 111, Folder 1224)
  - #131, East Caribbean Biodiversity Program, Kevel Lindsay, Bruce Horwith, Restoration of Offshore Island and Conservation of Biodiversity in Antigua-Barbuda, 1996 (Box 111, Folder 1225)
  - #131, East Caribbean Biodiversity Program, Vegetation Classification of Antigua, Barbuda, and Redonda, 1997 (Box 111, Folder 1226)
  - #131, East Caribbean Biodiversity Program, Biodiversity Profile of Antigua, Barbuda, and Redonda, 1997 (Box 111, Folder 1227)
  - #131, East Caribbean Biodiversity Program, Seabird Conservation Status Report, Antigua, Barbuda, and Redonda, 1997 (Box 111, Folder 1228)
  - #131, East Caribbean Biodiversity Program, United Nations Development Programme (UNDP) Consultancy Report, 1998-1999 (Box 111, Folder 1229-1230)
  - #131, East Caribbean Biodiversity Program, Vegetation Classification of St. Kitts and Nevis, 1999 (Box 111, Folder 1231)
  - #131, East Caribbean Biodiversity Program, Biodiversity Profile of St. Kitts and Nevis, 1999 (Box 111, Folder 1232)
  - #131, East Caribbean Biodiversity Program, Brimstone Hill Survey, 1998 (Box 111, Folder 1233)
  - #131, East Caribbean Biodiversity Program, Charter Yachts for Coastal Conservation, 1995 (Box 111, Folder 1234)
  - #131, East Caribbean Biodiversity Program, Regarding Bird Conservation Project, 1996-2000, 2002 (Box 112, Folder 1235)
  - #131, East Caribbean Biodiversity Program, Invasive Species, 2003 (Box 112, Folder 1236)
  - #131, East Caribbean Biodiversity Program, West Indian Vegetation Mapping Project, 1998-2000 (Box 112, Folder 1237)
  - #131, East Caribbean Biodiversity Program, Correspondence with UK Conservation Groups, 1995, 1997, 1997 (Box 112, Folder 1238)
  - #131, East Caribbean Biodiversity Program, United Nations Development Programme (UNDP), GEF Support Programme, 1997-1998 (Box 112, Folder 1239)
  - #131, East Caribbean Biodiversity Program, Correspondence with IITF, 1995 (Box 112, Folder 1240)
  - #131, East Caribbean Biodiversity Program, Correspondence with American Museum of Natural History, 1997 (Box 112, Folder 1241)
  - #132, MacArthur Foundation-Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) II, Proposal, Grant Negotiations, Award, 1991-1993 (Box 112, Folder 1242)
  - #132, MacArthur Foundation-Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) II, Correspondence with MacArthur Foundation, 1994-1998 (Box 112, Folder 1243)
  - #132, MacArthur Foundation-Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) II, Annual Reports to MacArthur Foundation, 1994, 1996, 1998 (Box 112, Folder 1244)
  - #132, MacArthur Foundation-Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) II, Correspondence with VIRMC Members, 1993-1996, 1999 (Box 112, Folder 1245)
  - #132, MacArthur Foundation-Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) II, Correspondence with VI National Park, 1982, 1994-1997, 1999 (Box 112, Folder 1246)
  - #132, MacArthur Foundation-Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) II, University of VI Correspondence, 1993 (Box 112, Folder 1247)
  - #132, MacArthur Foundation-Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) II, Internal Correspondence and Personnel, 1995-1996 (Box 112, Folder 1248)
  - #132, MacArthur Foundation-Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) II, Cataloging Eastern Caribbean Center/IRF Library Collection, 1993-1995, 1997 (Box 113, Folder 1249)
  - #132, MacArthur Foundation-Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) II, Clippings, Public Relations, Announcements, etc., 1996 (Box 113, Folder 1250)
  - #132, MacArthur Foundation-Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) II, VIRMC Brochure, 1994 (Box 113, Folder 1251)
  - #132, MacArthur Foundation-Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) II, The Nature Conservancy (TNC), University of VI Conservation Data Center, 1994-2001, 20003 (Box 113, Folder 1252)
  - #132, MacArthur Foundation-Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) II, VIRMC Internet Mail List Postings, 1998-2001 (Box 113, Folder 1253)
  - #132, MacArthur Foundation-Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) II, VIRMC Geographical Informational Systems Program, 1992, 1994-1996 (Box 113, Folder 1254)
  - #132, MacArthur Foundation-Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) II, Richard Volk "Futures" Documentation, 1993-1994 (Box 113, Folder 1255)
  - #132, MacArthur Foundation-Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) II, Project Ideas, Concepts, 1994-1995 (Box 113, Folder 1256)
  - #133, International Institute of Tropical Forestry (IITF) Project, Antigua, Montserrat, Proposal and Award Documentation, 1993 (Box 113, Folder 1257)
  - #133, International Institute of Tropical Forestry (IITF) Project, Antigua, Montserrat, Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 113, Folder 1258)
  - #133, International Institute of Tropical Forestry (IITF) Project, Antigua, Montserrat, Montserrat Project, 1993-1995 (Box 113, Folder 1259)
  - #133, International Institute of Tropical Forestry (IITF) Project, Antigua, Montserrat, Wallings Reservoir, Antigua Project, 1994-1995 (Box 113, Folder 1260)
  - #133, International Institute of Tropical Forestry (IITF) Project, Antigua, Montserrat, Quarterly Reports, 1993-1995 (Box 113, Folder 1261)
  - #133, International Institute of Tropical Forestry (IITF) Project, Antigua, Montserrat, Final Report, 1996 (Box 113, Folder 1262)
  - #134, Sedimentation Study, Proposal, 1993 (Box 113, Folder 1263)
  - #134, Sedimentation Study, Contract, Memorandum of Understanding, 1994 (Box 113, Folder 1264)
  - #134, Sedimentation Study, General Correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 113, Folder 1265)
  - #134, Sedimentation Study, Correspondence with Caribbean Environmental and Development Institute, 1994 (Box 113, Folder 1266)
  - #134, Sedimentation Study, Correspondence with United Nations Environment Programme (Regional Coordinating Unit/Caribbean Environment Programme), 1993-1995 (Box 113, Folder 1267)
  - #134, Sedimentation Study, Guidelines for United Nations Environment Programme, 1995 (Box 113, Folder 1268)
  - #135, United Nations Environment Programme (UNEP) Coastal Plan, Proposal and Contract, 1994 (Box 113, Folder 1269)
  - #135, United Nations Environment Programme (UNEP) Coastal Plan, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1995 (Box 113, Folder 1270)
  - #135, United Nations Environment Programme (UNEP) Coastal Plan, Correspondence with Team Members, 1994 (Box 113, Folder 1271)
  - #135, United Nations Environment Programme (UNEP) Coastal Plan, Correspondence with UNEP, 1994-1995 (Box 114, Folder 1272)
  - #135, United Nations Environment Programme (UNEP) Coastal Plan, Integrated Coastal Area Management Guidelines for UNEP, 1995 (Box 114, Folder 1273)
  - #136, Jackson Hole Preserve NGO Grant, Proposal and Grant Award, 1994-1995 (Box 114, Frame 1274)
  - #137, Environmental Impact Assessment (EIA), Water Colonies, Background Material, 1996 (Box 114, Folder 1275)
  - #137, Environmental Impact Assessment (EIA), Water Colonies, Contract, 1995 (Box 114, Folder 1276)
  - #137, Environmental Impact Assessment (EIA), Water Colonies, Personnel, 1995 (Box 114, Folder 1277)
  - #137, Environmental Impact Assessment (EIA), Water Colonies, Correspondence with the British Virgin Islands, 1995 (Box 114, Folder 1278)
  - #137, Environmental Impact Assessment (EIA), Water Colonies, Correspondence with Onions, Buchard and McCulloch and Cal-Quality Land Corporation, 1995 (Box 114, Folder 1279)
  - #137, Environmental Impact Assessment (EIA), Water Colonies, Reports, 1995 (Box 114, Folder 1280)
  - #137, Environmental Impact Assessment (EIA), Water Colonies Resort, Report, 1995 (Box 114, Folder 1281)
  - #137, Environmental Impact Assessment (EIA), Water Colonies Resort, Addendum, 1997 (Box 114, Folder 1282)
  - #138, Virgin Islands Disaster Plan Update, Background Information, 1996 (Box 114, Folder 1283)
  - #138, Virgin Islands Disaster Plan Update, Proposal and Contract, 1995 (Box 114, Folder 1284)
  - #138, Virgin Islands Disaster Plan Update, Personnel, 1995-1996 (Box 114, Folder 1285)
  - #138, Virgin Islands Disaster Plan Update, Correspondence with VI Government, 1995-1996 (Box 114, Folder 1286)
  - #138, Virgin Islands Disaster Plan Update, Reports, 1995 (Box 114, Folder 1287)
  - #138, Virgin Islands Disaster Plan Update, Mitigating the Impact of Natural Hazards in the USVI, 1995 (Box 114, Folder 1288)
  - #139, World Wildlife Fund (WWF)-UK Biodiversity Support, Proposals and Contracts with WWF-UK, 1995 (Box 114, Folder 1289)
  - #139, World Wildlife Fund (WWF)-UK Biodiversity Support, Internal Project Correspondence, 1996 (Box 114, Folder 1290)
  - #139, World Wildlife Fund (WWF)-UK Biodiversity Support, Correspondence with Montserrat Trust, 1996 (Box 114, Folder 1291)
  - #139, World Wildlife Fund (WWF)-UK Biodiversity Support, Correspondence with WWF-UK, 1995-1996 (Box 115, Folder 1292)
  - #139, World Wildlife Fund (WWF)-UK Biodiversity Support, Reports and Documentation, 1996 (Box 115, Folder 1293)
  - #140, United Nations Environment Programme (UNEP), Tourism and Coastal Best Management Practices, Proposal and Contract with UNEP, 1996 (Box 115, Folder 1294)
  - #140, United Nations Environment Programme (UNEP), Tourism and Coastal Best Management Practices, Exclusive Economic Zone Mapping for Wider Caribbean, 1996 (Box 115, Folder 1295)
  - #140, United Nations Environment Programme (UNEP), Tourism and Coastal Best Management Practices, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1996 (Box 115, Folder 1296)
  - #140, United Nations Environment Programme (UNEP), Tourism and Coastal Best Management Practices, Correspondence with UNEP and Agency for International Development, 1996-1997 (Box 115, Folder 1297)
  - #140, United Nations Environment Programme (UNEP), Tourism and Coastal Best Management Practices, Coastal Resources Degradation, 1996 (Box 115, Folder 1298)
  - #141, Antigua Marine Park, Proposal and Contract, 1996 (Box 115, Folder 1299)
  - #141, Antigua Marine Park, Personnel, 1996-1997 (Box 115, Folder 1300)
  - #141, Antigua Marine Park, Internal Correspondence and Personnel, 1996-1997 (Box 115, Folder 1301)
  - #141, Antigua Marine Park, Environmental Awareness Group Sub-Contract, 1996-1997, 2000 (Box 115, Folder 1302)
  - #141, Antigua Marine Park, Public Meeting, 1996 (Box 115, Folder 1303)
  - #141, Antigua Marine Park, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1996 (Box 115, Folder 1304)
  - #141, Antigua Marine Park, Correspondence with Organization of American States and Government of Antigua, 1996-1997 (Box 115, Folder 1305)
  - #141, Antigua Marine Park, Reports, 1996 (Box 115, Folder 1306)
  - #141, Parham Harbour Facilitation, Characterization of Marine Resources, 1996 (Box 115, Folder 1307)
  - #141, Parham Harbour Facilitation, Flora of the Offshore Islands, 1996 (Box 115, Folder 1308)
  - #141, Parham Harbour Facilitation, Nesting Birds of the Offshore Islands and Adjacent Shorelines, 19996 (Box 115, Folder 1309)
  - #141, Parham Harbour Facilitation, Pollution Stresses and Impacts, 1996 (Box 115, Folder 1310)
  - #141, Parham Harbour Facilitation, Usage Patterns and the Resources Management Perceptions of Users, 1996 (Box 115, Folder 1311)
  - #141, Parham Harbour Facilitation, Management Plan for the Bird Island Marine Reserve, 1997 (Box 116, Folder 1312)
  - #142, St. John Forest Dynamics, Proposal and Contract, 1996 (Box 116, Folder 1313)
  - #142, St. John Forest Dynamics, Internal Correspondence, 1997-1999 (Box 116, Folder 1314)
  - #142, St. John Forest Dynamics, Correspondence with Homeland Foundation, 1997-1999 (Box 116, Folder 1315)
  - #143, Virgin Islands Biological Information Node, Proposal and Contract, 1996-1997 (Box 116, Folder 1316)
  - #143, Virgin Islands Biological Information Node, Training and Workshops, 1996-1997 (Box 116, Folder 1317)
  - #143, Virgin Islands Biological Information Node, Internal Correspondence and Personnel, 1996-1997 (Box 116, Folder 1318)
  - #143, Virgin Islands Biological Information Node, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 116, Folder 1319)
  - #143, Virgin Islands Biological Information Node, Correspondence with University of VI, Conservation Data center, The Nature Conservancy (TNC), 1996-1998 (Box 116, Folder 1320)
  - #143, Virgin Islands Biological Information Node, Correspondence with US Geological Survey, 1996-1998 (Box 116, Folder 1321)
  - #143, Virgin Islands Biological Information Node, Reports and Documentation, 1996-1998 (Box 116, Folder 1322)
  - #144, Wellhead Inventory, Proposal and Contract, 1995-1996 (Box 116, Folder 1323)
  - #144, Wellhead Inventory, Personnel and Internal Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 116, Folder 1324)
  - #144, Wellhead Inventory, Correspondence with Virgin Islands Government Agencies, 1996-1998 (Box 116, Folder 1325)
  - #144, Wellhead Inventory, Performance and Financial Reports, 1996-1997 (Box 116, Folder 1326)
  - #144, Wellhead Inventory, Documents and Reports, 1994, 1997 (Box 116, Folder 1328)
  - #145, Virgin Islands Vegetation Mapping, The Nature Conservancy (TNC), Proposal and Contract, 1996 (Box 116, Folder 1328)
  - #145, Virgin Islands Vegetation Mapping, The Nature Conservancy (TNC), Personnel and Internal Correspondence, 1996 (Box 116, Folder 1329)
  - #145, Virgin Islands Vegetation Mapping, The Nature Conservancy (TNC), Correspondence with TNC, Conservation Data Center, ECC, Virgin Islands Government, 1996-1997 (Box 116, Folder 1330)
  - #145, Virgin Islands Vegetation Mapping, The Nature Conservancy (TNC), Background Documentation, 1996 (Box 116, Folder 1331)
  - #146, Small Projects, Anegada Turtles, Panaphil Foundation, 1996-1997 (Box 117, Folder 1332)
  - #146, Small Projects, Antigua Climate Change Workshop, 1998-1999 (Box 117, Folder 1333)
  - #146, Small Projects, British Virgin Islands Conservation, Grant by Robins Foundation, 2005, 2007-2015 (Box 117, Folder 1334)
  - #146, Small Projects, British Virgin Islands, Jarecki Grants, 1999, 2001 (Box 117, Folder 1335)
  - #146, Small Projects, British Virgin Islands Paraquita Bay, Environmental Impact Assessment, 1997 (Box 117, Folder 1336)
  - #146, Small Projects, Caribbean Philanthropy Network, 2010-2011 (Box 117, Folder 1337)
  - #146, Small Projects, Dominica Caribs, Jarecki, 2000-2002 (Box 117, Folder 1338)
  - #146, Small Projects, The Faile Foundation, British Virgin Islands, Green Virgin Islands, 2011-2014 (Box 117, Folder 1339)
  - #146, Small Projects, Oil Nut Bay Environmental Impact Assessment, Virgin Gorda, British Virgin Islands, 1999-2001, 2003 (Box 117, Folder 1340)
  - #146, Small Projects, Oil Nut Bay, British Virgin Islands, Final Report, 2001 (Box 117, Folder 1341)
  - #146, Small Projects, Organization of American States, Internet Training, 1996-1997 (Box 117, Folder 1342)
  - #146, Small Projects, Oversea Territories Program Fund, British Virgin Islands Governor's Office, 2013-2015 (Box 117, Folder 1343)
  - #146, Small Projects, Pockwood pond, British Virgin Islands, 2001-2003 (Box 118, Folder 1344)
  - #146, Small Projects, SIDSNET Training, 1999-2000 (Box 118, Folder 1345)
  - #146, Small Projects, Survey of St. John's Bats, 2007-2008 (Box 118, Folder 1346)
  - #146, Small Projects, Survey of St. John's Bats-Bats, BCI Report, Final, 2008 (Box 118, Folder 1346)
  - #146, Small Projects, UN Environment Programme (UNEP) Regional Office for Latin America and the Caribbean, Rewrite of State of the Environment Chapter, 1999-2000 (Box 118, Folder 1347)
  - #146, Small Projects, Mosquito Island, British Virgin Islands, A Terrestrial Resource Characterization, 2007 (Box 118, Folder 1348)
  - #146, Small Projects, Nanny Cay, Tortola, British Virgin Islands, A Terrestrial Resource Characterization, 2010 (Box 118, Folder 1349)
  - #147, St. John Sedimentation Project, Proposal and Contract, 1996 (Box 118, Folder 1350)
  - #147, St. John Sedimentation Project, Publicity, Hand-Outs, etc., 1996, 1999 (Box 118, Folder 1351)
  - #147, St. John Sedimentation Project, Personnel and Internal Correspondence, 1997-2000 (Box 118, Folder 1352)
  - #147, St. John Sedimentation Project, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1996-2000 (Box 118, Folder 1353)
  - #147, St. John Sedimentation Project, Correspondence with Virgin Islands Government Agencies, 1996-2000 (Box 118, Folder 1354)
  - #147, St. John Sedimentation Project, Correspondence with Virgin Islands National Park and Colorado State University, 1993, 1996-2000 (Box 118, Folder 1355)
  - #147, St. John Sedimentation Project, Prior Sedimentation Project, 1996 (Box 118, Folder 1356)
  - #147, St. John Sedimentation Project, Phase 3 and 4, Proposal and Memorandum of Agreement, 1996-1999 (Box 118, Folder 1357)
  - #147, St. John Sedimentation Project, Research Reports, 1997-2000 (Box 118, Folder 1358)
  - #148, Antigua Ecosystem Classification, Proposal and Contract, 1996 (Box 119, Folder 1359)
  - #148, Antigua Ecosystem Classification, Miscellaneous Correspondence, Information, 1997 (Box 119, Folder 1360)
  - #148, Antigua Ecosystem Classification, Internal Correspondence, 1997 (Box 119, Folder 1361)
  - #148, Antigua Ecosystem Classification, Correspondence with The Nature Conservancy (TNC), Conservation Data Center, 1996-1997 (Box 119, Folder 1362)
  - #148, Antigua Ecosystem Classification, The Nature Conservancy (TNC) Workshop, 1996 (Box 119, Folder 1363)
  - #148, Antigua Ecosystem Classification, Reports to The Nature Conservancy (TNC), 1997 (Box 119, Folder 1364)